usbornebooksathome.co.uk 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy Usborne Books at Home

**Usborne Privacy Policy**

In order for you to participate in our competitions or for us to send you free materials such as posters, badges and bookmarks, it is necessary for you to provide us with personal information, such as your name, email address, age and postal address. After sending you materials or notifying you that you have won a competition, your personal information will not be retained on our files, unless you have indicated that you would like to receive the Usborne email newsletter. 

You can unsubscribe from the newsletter email at any time by following the instructions on the Website, or by writing to the address at the end of this page, and your details will be removed from our files. Children under the age of 13 must ask permission of an adult before entering a competition or sending any personal information. Whenever you provide personal information, we will treat that information in accordance both with this policy and with current UK legislation

Usborne Publishing will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. For the purpose of these terms Usborne Publishing Ltd is the data controller. Any information you provide to Usborne Publishing will only be used within Usborne Publishing, and will never be supplied to third parties without first obtaining your consent, or as required or permitted by law. If you are under 18, please make sure that you obtain your parent/guardian's permission before you provide your personal information to the Usborne Website.

**How to contact Usborne Publishing**

This Website is owned and operated by Usborne Publishing Ltd. If you have any questions about this Website or our privacy policy, please write or email us at the following addresses:

Robert Jones  
Usborne Publishing Ltd   
83-85 Saffron Hill   
London   
EC1N 8RT   
UK 

Telephone: 0044 (0)20 7430 2800 email: [privacy_policy@usborne.com ](mailto:mail@privacy_policy@usborne.com)
